<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://dataluminosity.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2017 Data Luminosity by Private Analytics</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dataluminosity.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CrowdZen</title>
      <link>https://dataluminosity.github.io/portfolio/crowdzen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dataluminosity.github.io/portfolio/crowdzen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Real-time privacy-preserving activity levels. First known public open data privacy-presrving campus deployment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joshua Joy, Martin Verde, Keshav Tadimeti, Tyler Lindberg, Mario Gerla&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LocationSafe</title>
      <link>https://dataluminosity.github.io/portfolio/locationsafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:44:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dataluminosity.github.io/portfolio/locationsafe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First design and implementation of a privacy module built into the GPSD daemon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joshua Joy, Minh Le, Mario Gerla&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DiscoverFriends</title>
      <link>https://dataluminosity.github.io/portfolio/discoverfriends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dataluminosity.github.io/portfolio/discoverfriends/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DiscoverFriends: Secure social network communication in mobile ad hoc networks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first Android multi-hop WiFi direct protocol using IPv6.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This paper presents a secure communication application called DiscoverFriends.  Its purpose is to securely communicate to a group of online friends while bypassing their respective social networking servers under a mobile ad hoc network environment. DiscoverFriends leverages Bloom filters and a hybrid encryption technique with a self-organized public-key management scheme to securely identify friends and provide authentication. Additionally, DiscoverFriends enables anonymous location check-ins by utilizing a new cryptographic primitive called Function Secret Sharing. Finally, to the best of our knowledge, DiscoverFriends implements and evaluates the first Android multi-hop WiFi direct protocol using IPv6.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>